

### **SUMMARY**

I am designer with a strong blend of creativity and front-end web development to create dynamic user experiences. I am a motivated self-starter who has the ability to transform ideas into user friendly, captivating designs and deliver results in a fast-paced environment. I am currently working on a web design and development graduate certificate at Denver University.

#### SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, jQuery/JavaScript, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, User Experience/User Interaction, Responsive Web Design, Git/Github, Logo/Branding/Styleguide

## **EXPERIENCE**

RTD

2013-Present

Graphic/Web Designer

As a designer, I am responsible for the comprehension of the brand and bringing it to life in form of best in-class customer experiences. I worked on award-winning creative campaigns, as well as base level system projects.

- Worked on converting the RTD main site to be responsive by the combination of fluid images, fluid grids, and media queries. Used digital style guide with similar framework as Bootstrap to convert web pages to be responsive.
- Redesigned the base system information platforms for RTD users; including bus stop signs, schedules and shutter boards. Focused on the user experience through the redesign process.
- Lead designer on the opening of East Rail Line to the Airport in 2016. Working on creating mini site for the 4 rail lines opening in 2016. The site will be engaging and informational for the end users.

# Hogan Lovells, Denver, CO

2011 - 2012

Contract designer

Responsible for the design of graphic applications such as collateral material, custom proposal graphics, ads, info sheets, custom invitations, signage, firm publications, and electronic invites and communications.

- Successfully worked remotely along side a designer in Washington, D.C. and a creative director in New York.
- Collaborated with various clients: marketing team members, lawyers, support staff, and designers.
- Designed website wireframes, HTML emails, announcements and e-newsletter campaigns.

## MoneyGram, Lakewood, CO

2009 - 2011

Contract Designer

I supported the marketing department by creating media such as direct mail, advertisements, brochures, presentations, signage, promotional materials and collaterals as needed. Acted as a liaison between the Denver and Dallas offices during relocation transition.

## Munchkin, Inc. North Hills, CA

2006 - 2011

Senior Graphic Designer

As a senior designer, I lead a team of 3 in house designers as well as designers in our Hong Kong office to help produce print and packaging for baby and pet products. Projects included annual sales catalog, packaging designs, tradeshow materials and sales presentations.

## Patina Group, Los Angeles, CA

2005 - 2006

Graphic Designer

I worked alongside the marketing team to help maintain Patina Group's unique upscale dining experience at landmark locations in Los Angeles and New York. Created various materials for Restaurant Associates + Patina Group such as menus, promotional mailers, sales sheets and catalogs. Negotiated and maintained printing cost, reviewed and attend the final press-checks.

# **EDUCATION**

University of Denver

Graduate Certificate, Advanced Study in Web Design and Development, 2014 - 2015

California State University-Long Beach

Bachelor of Fine Arts (BFA), Graphic Design, 2000 - 2004

References available upon request.